<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<author>
		<name>
			Kevin Renskers
		</name>
	</author>
	<title type="text">Loopwerk</title>
	<id>https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/tag/random/feed.xml</id>
	<link href="https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/tag/random/feed.xml" rel="self">
	</link>
	<updated>2024-02-27T16:12:13Z</updated>
	<generator uri="https://github.com/loopwerk/Saga">
		Saga
	</generator>
	<entry>
		<title type="text">2023 in review</title>
		<id>https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2023/2023-in-review/</id>
		<link href="https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2023/2023-in-review/" rel="alternate">
		</link>
		<updated>2023-12-28T16:00:00Z</updated>
		<summary type="text">
			Another year in review - even though it feels like I wrote the previous one not so long ago. Time flies and it’s flying faster and faster each and every year.
		</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title type="text">2022 in review</title>
		<id>https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2022/2022-in-review/</id>
		<link href="https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2022/2022-in-review/" rel="alternate">
		</link>
		<updated>2022-12-14T16:00:00Z</updated>
		<summary type="text">
			Another year flew by, I can&apos;t really believe it&apos;s already been a whole year since I wrote 2021 in review. A very busy and somewhat stressful year - although not for all the reasons I predicted a year ago.
		</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title type="text">2021 in review</title>
		<id>https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2021/2021-in-review/</id>
		<link href="https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2021/2021-in-review/" rel="alternate">
		</link>
		<updated>2021-12-28T16:00:00Z</updated>
		<summary type="text">
			Welcome to the end of 2021, a.k.a. the second year of the pandemic. Another year of not going abroad, barely seeing friends, playing Dungeons &amp; Dragons via Zoom instead of at the table. A year of mild depression and feelings of loneliness. But also a year of hope when we all got access to the vaccines and when we didn&apos;t hear about Trump every day in the news. And last but not least: it was also a very productive year!
		</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title type="text">Interview with proglib.io</title>
		<id>https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2021/interview-proglib/</id>
		<link href="https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2021/interview-proglib/" rel="alternate">
		</link>
		<updated>2021-07-10T16:00:00Z</updated>
		<summary type="text">
			Recently I was interviewed for the Russian IT website proglib.io. Since it might be interesting for non-Russian speakers, here it is in the original English version.
		</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title type="text">2016 in review</title>
		<id>https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2016/2016-in-review/</id>
		<link href="https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2016/2016-in-review/" rel="alternate">
		</link>
		<updated>2016-12-18T16:00:00Z</updated>
		<summary type="text">
			It’s that time of year again to look back and reflect at everything you’ve done and achieved, and to make plans for the next year. 2016 was a pretty big year for me, both personally and professionally. 
In the end of August 2015 I moved back from...
		</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title type="text">Looking back at 2012</title>
		<id>https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2012/looking-back-2012/</id>
		<link href="https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2012/looking-back-2012/" rel="alternate">
		</link>
		<updated>2012-12-25T16:00:00Z</updated>
		<summary type="text">
			On January 2 I moved to Iceland with two suitcases and a job contract. My new title: iOS developer at Gangverk, a small company creating iPhone- and Android apps for CBS in the United States. This was the beginning of an amazing year for me, both...
		</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title type="text">Designing my very own ideal programming language</title>
		<id>https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2011/designing-my-very-own-ideal-programming-language/</id>
		<link href="https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2011/designing-my-very-own-ideal-programming-language/" rel="alternate">
		</link>
		<updated>2011-04-23T16:00:00Z</updated>
		<summary type="text">
			In 2009 I made the switch to Python, after having worked exclusively with PHP and Javascript for almost a decade. I really like the language, much more than I ever liked PHP. Of course it’s not perfect (see one of my first posts called Things I hate...
		</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title type="text">Switching from MobileMe &amp; my short adventure with Google App Engine</title>
		<id>https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2009/switching-mobileme-my-short-adventure-google-app-engine/</id>
		<link href="https://www.loopwerk.io/articles/2009/switching-mobileme-my-short-adventure-google-app-engine/" rel="alternate">
		</link>
		<updated>2009-10-20T16:00:00Z</updated>
		<summary type="text">
			I can’t remember how long ago it’s been that I’ve used a free email address like hotmail, yahoo or gmail. For more than 8 years I’ve used my own domain names to host my email. In the very beginning on my own little server at home, later on a “real”...
		</summary>
	</entry>
</feed>